Once you've initialized Tessle in your
project, it's recommended that you
integrate Tessle with your preferred AI
coding agent. In this video, we'll show
you how to connect Tessle with Gemini
CLI.
At a terminal, from within your project
route, run Tessle setup agent. This will
give you a list of agents you can pick
from. We'll select Gemini CLI and let
Tesla auto configure the MCP
integration. That's it. Now when I run
Gemini CLI, it picks up the Tessle MCP
server straight away and is ready to
use.
You've now got Tessle connected as an
MCP server within Gemini CLI. Your next
step is to use the spec registry or
Tessle framework.